hey real quick white leftists stop calling me you stop it i keep seeing white leftists come
on my page say shit like you know us american leftists we ain't us american leftists do not
include me with you do not we may have similar political points of view do not include me in
anything that is us american leftists do not before i'm a leftist i'm black i'm a woman i'm
from the caribbean i mean there's there's so many things i am before having similar views as people
who consider themselves leftists stop it and the fact that you call yourself us american leftist
says enough leave me out of that shit you sound fucking ridiculous us american leftists
you even calling yourself american means you ain't left enough how black am i gonna have to get
the whole uh liberation of oppressed people in the united states had to do not with climbing up some
ladder to success not for asking to be just like rockefeller or just like dupont or just like
ford because that would only continue the oppression and exploitation of oppressed people
in the united states and specifically african people born and raised in the united states